度过几分钟如几小时
Minutes like hours
度过几小时如数天
Hours like days
我焦躁地等着
I wait, impatient
又饿又疯
Hungry and crazed
几步之遥
A few steps away
一扇门之外
One door apart
一声招呼就会击碎我受伤的心
One hello to break my healing heart
如果我之前能在地上挖洞
If I could dig a hole in the ground
如果我之前能转过身去
If I could turn around
如果我之前能一声不吭
If I could make no sound
我现在会这么做
I would
度过数个星期如度过数月
Weeks like months
度过数月如度过多年
Months like years
度过多年如度过多个年代
Years like decades
而泪流成河
And river for tears
我大吃一惊
I threw a fit
我感到崩溃
I lost my shit
你离我只有一步之遥而我必须对此无视
You're one step away and I can't think of it
如果我之前能在地上挖洞
If I could dig a hole in the ground
如果我之前能转过身去
If I could turn around
如果我之前能一声不吭
If I could make no sound
我现在会这么做
I would
这过去很久了
It's been too long
但还是不够去遗忘
Not enough to forget
因为我还不够强大
That I'm not that strong
至少现在还不够
At least not yet
如果我之前能一声不吭
If I could make no sound
我确信我现在会这么做
Surely I would
如果我之前能在地上挖洞
If I could dig a hole in the ground
如果我之前能转过身去
If I could turn around
如果我之前能
If I could
我现在会这么做
I would